Guide to the Art Torres Papers, ca. 1970-1994 M0881
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Insurance Comm[ittee] Hearing on Earthquake Insurance Postponed, 2/19/1992 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Positive Profile of Art Torres, Sacramento Bee, Feb 16, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Sen[ate] Insurance Comm[ittee] to Hold Special Hearing on Earthquake Ins[urance], 2/10/1992 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Senate to Vote on Prop[osition] 103, Rate Rollbacks, 2/10/1992 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- No Campaign Money from Insurers, Trial Lawyers Association, 2/3/1992 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Senate Rules Committee Approves Subpoena of L.A. CTY Sheriff's Dept. Records, Jan 9, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Torres Backs Bonds for Schools, Feb 4, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Prop[osition] 103 Insurance Refunds, Feb 4, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Torres on Wilson Trip to D.C., Feb 4, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- The Trials of Art Torres, The Sacto Bee, Feb 2, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Torres Vow on Insurance Comm[ittee], 1/29/1992 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Torres, Public Employee Coalition to Intro[ductive] Measure to 'Cut Red Tape' in Insurance and Health Care Forms (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Statement of Senator Torres Regarding the Illegality of the Sup[reme] Court's State and Congressional Plans (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Torres to Head Powerful Senate Insurance Comm[ittee], 1/22/1992 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Leg[islative] Panel to Hold 2 Hearings in No[rthern] Ca[lifornia] on Police Conduct toward the Native American Community (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Wilson's off the Mark on Immigrants (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Press Release Index, 1992/1993 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Assembly Bill 1943 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Senate Bill 1335, Police (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Channel One: Press (Box 50, Folder 24)
- UCSC Internship Program (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Senate Bill 65, General (Box 50, Folder 26)
- Senate Bill 65, Don Dixon (Box 50, Folder 27)
- Auto Insurance Package (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Note: Box contains clippings. (Box 51)
- Budget Select Items, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Budget Review, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Health Care (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1333, Health Data Bill (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Chicano Studies (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Chevron / PBS Event (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Senate (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Clippings, miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 8)
- LA River: Senate Bill 20 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- First AME Spcech (Box 51, Folder 10)
- South Pasadena (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Budget (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Budget FY, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- East Los Angeles Prison (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Budget, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Budget Requests, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Budget File, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Multicultural Institute (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Governor's Veto to Budget (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Possible Budget Overrides (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Hispanic Caucus (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Community Colleges, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Human Corps (Box 52, Folder 10)
- CORO Foundation (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Note: Box contains clippings, memorabilia. (Box 53)
- Community Colleges (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Non AT Press Releases (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Kennedy, Edward (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Edward M. Kennedy (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Kennedy Buttons (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Recent OUI [?] (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Kathleen Decker Profile (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Allen's Clips - Recent (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Gann Initiative - Overwrite (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Mailing Lists, Pacific Rim Committee [?] (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Press Releases, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- $14 Million Funding Boost Keeps English Classes Open (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Clippings, etc. (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Potential Jobs / Placements (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Add to Press List (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Antarctica (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Rockwell Labs (Box 53, Folder 17)
- CSUS Academic Component (Box 54, Folder 1)
- K-12 Articles, Briefs, Bills (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Budget, General (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Sample Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Art Torres - Clips (Box 54, Folder 5)
- California Channel (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Public Relations (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Earthquake Issue (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Drog Hit: Century Cable (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Transportation Press (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Med-Fly (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Golden State Air (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Teen Suicide (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Latino / African American Redistricting L.A. (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Toxics (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Note: Box contains clippings and photos. (Box 55)
- Police Conduct Press (Box 55, Folder 1)
- To Be Filed (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Publications and Photos (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 49 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 50 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 52 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 84 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- CAL EPA (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 97 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 111 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Torres, Background Info (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 109, SLIAG - Education Funding, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 109, Co-author [?] (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 410, Drop-out Accountability (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1250, Earthquake Bond Act of 1989 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 46 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1358, Hate Violence: Higher Education, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 262, Significant Legislation, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1754, Significant Legislation, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Senate Constitutional Amendment 31 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1758 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 46 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2179, Significant Legislation, 1983-1984 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1452 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 44 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 80, Significant Legislation, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 47 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 6 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 48 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Senate Joint Resolution 19, Significant Legislation, 1985-1986 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Senate Joint Resolution 27, Significant Legislation, 1985-1986 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 2030, (Torres) Insurance (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 48, Hazardous Materials Management, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 49, Aboveground Storage Tanks, 1990-1991 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- School Site Toxics: Senate Bill 2262 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 584, 1st D'Murder (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 1884, Drug Testing Bill (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 1250, Proposition 122: Earthquake Bonds (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 123, Truck Accidents (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2263, revised Senate Bill 1049, Toxic Gas Releases (Box 62, Folder 3)
- L.A.Coliseum: Senate Bill 2879 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1049, Toxic Gas Releases and Emergency Response (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 2442, Hazardous Materials, Chap[ter?] 6.95 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1250 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1050, Aboveground Tanks (Box 63, Folder 2)
- 1989 Earthquake, Special Session (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1114, Deaf Access (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 112 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 123 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 240 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Toxic Legislation - Toxic Committee (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 51, Torres, Bill of Rights (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 836 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 836 (continued) (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 194 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 296 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 340 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 349 / 1049 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 583 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 584 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 585 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 586 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 603 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 741 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 752 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 837 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 838 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1575 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 921 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 903, Children's Services (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 925 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 925 (continued) (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 902, Workers Compensation Treatment (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1446 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1408 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 954 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 955 (original) (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1082 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 956 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1047, Out of State Subdivisions (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1048 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1333 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1394 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1258 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1335 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1127 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1707 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1708 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1763 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1709 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1899 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1764 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1641 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1174 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 9 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 2031 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 2030 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 51 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 11 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 49 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1250 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1250 (continued) (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 65 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 49, Hazardous Substances Liability (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 358, Independent Contractors: Interpreters (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 358 (continued) (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1335 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 130, California Children Services' Program (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 206, Insurance: Agents (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 297, Health Plan Profits (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 38, California Health Reform Act of 1993 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 220, Medi-Cal Managed Care (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 240, LACTC Revenue Bond Act Repeal (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 590, Health Insurance Access and Equity Act (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 503 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 591, San Gabriel Basin Water Quality (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 684, Insurance: Motor Vehicles (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 700, Child Care and Development: Contractors (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 697, Property Taxation: Hospitals (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 698, STRS: Final Compensation (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 747, Earthquake Safety: Public Buildings (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 820, State Economic Development Financing Authority (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 903 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1047, Schools: Electronic Media (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1253, Cezar Chaves Holiday (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1106, Insurance: Anti-redlining (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Note: Box contains clippings. (Box 80)
- Senate Bill 1106 (continued) (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 926, Schools: Pupil Motivation and Maintenance Programs (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1009, Insurance: Public Insurance Advocate (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1027, Office of Immigrant and Refugee Affairs (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1046 - See Senate Bill 1253 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1054, CA Air and Space Center (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1075, Automobile Insurance Spot (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1231 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 1251, Peace Officers: Security Guards (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 1098, Insurance: Commercial (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1253 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1258, Undocumented Aliens: Convicted Felons, Deportation (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1279, Acupuncture: Peer Pressure (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1357, Insurance: Medicare Supplemental (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1367, Insurance: Liquidation (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1314 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1475, Insurance: Motor Vehicle Policy Terms (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 1355, Insurance: Homeowners Bill of Rights (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1374, Prison Warden Qualifications (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1381, Small Business Insurance (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1476, Medi-Cal Specialty Providers (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Note: Box contains clippings. (Box 83)
- Senate Bill 1373, Cezar Chaves Holiday (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1497, Newspaper of General Circulation (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1582, PERS: Military Service Credit (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1739, Public Building Safety (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1780, Health Insurance: Infertility Treatment Coverage (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1870, Earthquake Insurance (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1778, Insurance: Office of Public Advisor (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1816, Health Insurance (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1823, Public Safety Officer (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1833, Insurance Fraud Prevention (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1840, Insurance Disasters (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1871, Workers' Compensation (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1878, Undocumented Aliens; Convicted Felons, Deportation (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1884, Crime: Prostitution Harmful Matter (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 2012, Satellite Wagering License Fees (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 2009, Indian Gambling (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2028, Insurance (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2035, Firearms (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Senate Resolution 33, Northridge Earthquake (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Senate Constitutional Amendment 23, Insurance: Motor Vehicle, Pay at the Pump (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 12, PERS: Military Service Credit (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 14, Task Force on Multicultural Education and Research (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Letter to the Editor (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Note: Box contains clippings. (Box 86)
- January 1992 Clips (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1355, Homeowners Bill of Rights (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Gang Violence (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Oakland Fire Victims Press Clippings (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Unfair Claims Act (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Safety Letter [?] (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Porpoises [?] (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Earthquake Insurance (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Labor 1985 - present (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Marolin, 02.10.1994 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- California Economic Strategies (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Mailer (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Women (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Department of Insurance (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Auto (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Children (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Dentrues (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Foundation Center (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Faxes (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Crime (Box 87, Folder 9)
- New Ideas (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Three Strikes (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Violence in Government Offices, 12.07.1993 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Torres (Box 87, Folder 13)
- Insurance Fraud ICC, 12.09.1993 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Indian Affairs (Box 87, Folder 15)
- Women's Health, 12.14.1993 (Box 87, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous (Box 87, Folder 17)
- Op-Ed Positions (Box 87, Folder 18)
- Clinton Forest Plan (Box 87, Folder 19)
- Mailer (Box 87, Folder 20)
- Senate Bill 1258, Override (Box 87, Folder 21)
- Senate Bill 1314 [?] (Box 87, Folder 22)
- Note: Box contains clippings. (Box 88)
- EQ Bonds (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Education Folder (Box 88, Folder 2)
- DOI Conservation and Surplus Lines (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Letter to Longren - Immig[ration?] (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Wilson 1994 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Violence State Workers (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 838, Lifeguards to Stage, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Environmental Reorganization (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Press Release, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Torres Toxic Ash Bill Becomes Law (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Torres Toxic Package, Oct 7, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Senate Bill 50, Toxic Ash Bill, 10.16.1991 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- State Legis[lation?] Approves Reso[lution?] Urging SW Museum to Remain in Current Location (Box 88, Folder 14)
- Leg[islative?] Panel on Police Conduct to Hold 3d H[earing?] (Box 88, Folder 15)
- Selected Press Clippings (Senate Bill 112) (Box 88, Folder 16)
- Coalition of Latino and Immig[rant?] L[eaders?] Protest (Box 88, Folder 17)
- Torres Response to Fair Press Conf[erence] (Box 88, Folder 18)
- Resignation of U.C. Pres[ident?] Gardner (Box 88, Folder 19)
- Chemclear Scraps Toxic Proj[ect?] (Box 88, Folder 20)
- Senate Bill 112, Governor Says 'No' (Box 88, Folder 21)
- Torres to Speak / Employment Diser. against Latinos (Box 88, Folder 22)
- Torres Tells Governor No MedFly Spray (Box 88, Folder 23)
- Toxic Waste (Box 88, Folder 24)
- Anti-Trust Cases (Box 88, Folder 25)
- Anti-Trust (Box 88, Folder 26)
- If You Drink, Don't Drive (Box 88, Folder 27)
- Note: Box contains 4 audiotapes. (Box 89)
- Senate Bill 2747, Highways: Airspace Lease, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Zukin, James (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles Task Force (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Rebuild L.A. - Task Force (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles River Transit Committee (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 17, Workers' Compensation (Firefighters) (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Ramona Gardens (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Ramona Gardens, Hearing no.1 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Jimines Autopsy Report (Box 90, Folder 3)
- European Community (Box 90, Folder 4)
- L.A.R.T.C. - Mission Statement (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 102, Farm Labor Contractors (License Renewal) (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Note: Box contains clippings. (Box 91)
- Subcommittee on Peace Officer Conduct (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 264, Unemployment Insurance (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 437, Certificated Employees (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Judiciary Subcommittee on Peace Officer Conduct (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 260, School Districts (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 261, Unemployment Insurance (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Hughes Research Laboratories, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 262, Political Reform (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 40, Food and Drug (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 263, Medi-Cal (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 436, Employment (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 438, Public Employees (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 439, Psycho Therapist (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 440, Professional Advertising (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 737, Local Public Agency (Box 93, Folder 9)
- los Angeles River, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- L.A.R.T.C. Conference, Feb 8, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Attempt Murder of a Peace Officer, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Administrative Evaluation of Officer Involved Shooting, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 451, Arbitrary Movement of Children - Family (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 503 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 504, Foreclosures Fees (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 556, Pesticides (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 582, Student Financial Aid (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 583, Teacher Credentialing (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 584, Improvements (Stage Highways) (Box 94, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 735 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 741, School Buildings (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Note: Box contains photo materials and videotapes. (Box 95)
- Senate Bill 738, Pupil Health (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 736, Elections (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 739, Health Facilities (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 740, School Buildings (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Photo materials (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Senate Select Committee on the Pacific Rim, 8.12.1993 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Senate Education Committee (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Senate Energy and Public Utilities, 1993 (Box 95, Folder 8)